<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bus schedule - Novi Sad</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="add_lines">Add lines</string>
    <string name="urban">Urban</string>
    <string name="suburban">Suburban</string>
    <string name="work_day">Work day</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="click_the_plus_button_to_add_buses">Click the \"+\" button to add buses</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home screen</string>
    <string name="home_screen_text">When you open the app for the first time you will be presented with the home screen that doesn’t have any lines. If you want to add new lines to the home screen you need to click on the + button that will lead you to the add lines screen. In case you’ve opened the app before, the lines you’ve chosen the previous time you used it will be presented on the home screen for the current day of the week. The ability to change the schedule depending on the day of the week can be done by clicking on the desired day or by scrolling left-right. For every line displayed on the home screen it is shown the schedule for the previous, current and next hour, and in the absence of any of the three, the next three hours are added. By clicking on a collapsed card, it expands and shows the schedule for the whole day, while clicking again the card is collapsed to the nearest 3 hours. If. you desire to remove on of the lines, you can do so by long pressing the schedule to activate an option that offers you to delete the line from the home screen.</string>
    <string name="add_lines_screen">Add lines screen</string>
    <string name="add_lines_screen_text">When you open the add lines screen you will be shown urban lines. Switching between urban and suburban lines can be done by clicking on the tabs or by scrolling left-right. By clicking on one of the lines, it is being selected and added to the main screen, while clicking on already selected line it is being unselected and removed from the home screen.</string>
    <string name="settings_screen">Settings screen</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="Theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="update_app_text">The app is updated every time the driving season changes.</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="change_the_language_in_the_application">Change the language in the application</string>
    <string name="change_the_theme_in_the_application">Change the theme in the application</string>
    <string name="open_the_support_window">Open the support window</string>
    <string name="serbian">Serbian</string>
    <string name="choose_theme">Choose theme</string>
    <string name="rearrange_favorites_screen">Rearrange favorites screen</string>
    <string name="rearrange_screen_text">This screen contains all the lines you\'ve previously added to your home screen as your favorites, and on which you can rearrange them as you see fit.</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="availability">Availability</string>
    <string name="lines_availability_text">We wanted to let you know that the app also works in offline mode. What this means is that once all of the data is downloaded, you will be able to access desired bus schedules at times of need, even when you don\'t have internet connection.</string>
    <string name="default_theme">Default</string>
    <string name="sort_favorites">Sort favorites</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_text">On the settings screen you can change:\n
        \t3.1 Language\n
        \t\tClicking on language opens a dialog that allows you to select the language in which the content will be displayed.\n
        \t3.2 Theme\n
        \t\tClicking on theme opens a dialog that allows you to choose whether the application will be displayed with a dark or a light theme.
    </string>
    <string name="no_favorite_lines">You haven\'t added any lines to favorites</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_remove_line">Are you sure you want to remove this line?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="no_lines">Lines are not loaded. Check your internet connection.</string>

</resources>